<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Posts on Writing</title>
    <link>http://localhost:1313/posts/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Posts on Writing</description>
    <generator>Hugo</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Wed, 31 Dec 2025 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <atom:link href="http://localhost:1313/posts/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>The Professional</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/posts/professional/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 31 Dec 2025 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/posts/professional/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;On Sundays, the staff aired out the wards, as the stale air can be demanding on old lungs, and the only person who seemed to be taking advantage of the retirement of the cloth barriers that separated each bed was the grandparent. He had never given me a satisfactory answer as to why he belonged, and it was a mystery shared by all inhabitants of the ward. As I said, he didn’t seem to suggest mortality, except for his mild dementia and his eroded legs. This led me to suspect he had been dishonest about the severity of his condition.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>3.5 Hz</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/posts/35hz/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 23 Nov 2025 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/posts/35hz/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;He’s calling his girlfriend and she wants a new plastic face. People need to believe they’re better than others in some way, no matter how trivial, to keep going; myself included. But I have to be in this conversation, nominally, because we share the same blood, however distant. At least, that’s what my mother insists. The other relative—a cousin, I think—sits right next to him and scrolls through her phone as dinner is laid out before her. She speaks TikTok Japanese: the verbal equivalent of diarrhea. The father of the two asks too many questions about the future, so I lie to entertain myself. It’s what you have to do with people like him.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>My Debut as a Romance Novelist</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/posts/romance/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 29 Oct 2025 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/posts/romance/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;I might as well to kill myself.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Now, allow me to explain how I arrived at this conclusion, as I do not readily consider myself as the suicidal type. I confess that life treats me fairly well, and I have no immediate reason beyond the one I shall shortly provide; but bear with me, and I promise you will find yourself in the warmest realms of empathy.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;The crisis befell me on the nineteenth of October, the date of my birth. The day had started out just fine—in fact, I was in a good mood—when I awoke to find a blue paper bag resting on my table along with a note that read, Happy Birthday. At the thought of my roommate surreptitiously sneaking into my room late at night to leave the gift, I felt a certain warmth swelling within the crevices of my chest, as if warm milk had begun to leak from my heart. I arose from the bed, made my way to the desk, and peered into the bag, smiling in juvenile bliss:&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>The Equilibrium Girl</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/posts/equilibrium/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 28 Oct 2025 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/posts/equilibrium/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;When she got to college, she gained some weight. Lost some weight. Hated some people. Loved some people. Wished for death. Wished for life. But overall, she lived so that things would average out, and she could maintain, let’s say, some sort of equilibrium.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;She found friends worth her time. With them, she celebrated birthdays, visited tertiary people, danced at concerts. Crowded places are nice that way; you can forget a lot if you let yourself. Individuals blur into a larger mass, but if you were floating, looking down from above, you would understand that the crowd was less than the individual. She joined those crowds without much hesitation. When the speakers reverberated and the pandemonium belied her heart, it distracted her for a moment. Her friends would find her in the crowd and yell, &lt;em&gt;let’s dance!&lt;/em&gt; She yelled something back. It was difficult sober, but she could fall in love with vanity as long as there was enough alcohol.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>The Palindrome Woman and My Bladder</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/posts/palindrome/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 03 Oct 2025 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/posts/palindrome/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;Most people, I think, feel divorced from their past as long as enough time passes. Of course, not every piece of their identity is severed, but some parts are, and among them, I suspect embarrassing memories are the first to go. Whether these memories contribute to your identity at the present moment is beside the point. They once belonged to you, and with the passage of time, they drifted elsewhere.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Effort and Yield</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/posts/effort/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 28 Sep 2025 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/posts/effort/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;Exerting too much effort to complete a certain task is not uncommon. This is characteristic, especially of people who are habitually contrarian. Ideally, one exerts the least amount of effort possible to achieve the highest yield possible, but for various reasons, this is difficult to pull off. Hence, knowing, (1) when to exert effort, (2) how much of it to exert, and (3) the way in which it should be exerted, is necessary for optimal exertion. I will attempt an exploration of these three questions, but we must begin by defining effort and its result, which I will refer to as yield.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Starbucks</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/posts/starbucks/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 16 Sep 2025 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/posts/starbucks/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;The following is a list of my favorite Starbucks orders:&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;ul&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Spiced Chai Tea Latte&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Vanilla Bean Whipped Crème Frappuccino Blended Crème&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Iced Raspberry Pearl Pumpkin Spice Oatmilk Macchiato with Three Pumps of Brown Sugar Syrup, Three Pumps of Caramel Honey, and Three Pumps of Sugar-Free Vanilla Syrup (gotta stay healthy, ya know)&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Cold Pressed Strawberry Lemonade with No Strawberry or Lemons&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Crispy Crunch Oreo Crunch Crunch Hot Tea&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;I Like Wasting My Money Macchiato&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Girls LOVE Fish</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/posts/fish/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 11 Aug 2025 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/posts/fish/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;Ten years ago, I was waddling around my college campus going from one place to the next, with no real destination, as one does. I happened to be behind three guys, fraternity &amp;ldquo;brothers&amp;rdquo; to be precise. For ease of storytelling, let&amp;rsquo;s name them Gunner, Axel, and Thor. I don&amp;rsquo;t actually know their names but it&amp;rsquo;s apt and will make do for the time being.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Anyone walking past could tell they were real men. Now, Gunner&amp;rsquo;s haircut was a style I imagine one achieves by asking the barber for &amp;ldquo;the bald look&amp;rdquo;, starting at the sides, then leaving halfway through the haircut—just before the razor starts shaving away the top. I believe this style is called a &amp;ldquo;mullet&amp;rdquo;(?). I&amp;rsquo;m not too sure; I&amp;rsquo;ll have to ask around. In any case, that&amp;rsquo;s going to be my next haircut. Gunner&amp;rsquo;s hair reminded me of a Lego piece that I swear belonged to my Saturn V rocket I was gifted for Christmas at the age of five; the fingerprint of a real man. Axel had a tank top that was more tank than top; he ripped extra material off of it at the arms so that his thick nipples could see the light of day. By the same token, his armpit hair was exposed, glistening with beads of sweat and swaying in the wind, akin to turf after a rowdy football game. It inevitably occurred to me that I want to be like him when I grow up (VSK 2025). Finally, Thor, the manliest of them all, faced derision labeled as a &amp;ldquo;douche&amp;rdquo; though he and I knew that the hatred traced its origins to jealously, held a Monster in one hand and Penny skateboard in the other. He turned towards Gunner and Axel, looking straight into their eyes, preparing to drop what I expected to be the manliest shit I have ever heard. I knew, in this moment compressed between my failed past and my hopeful future, that this was the moment I had lived two decades for. Behind Thor&amp;rsquo;s aviators (even though it was cloudy), I could see the assured salvation. Since they were the manliest of men, I decided to listen intently, for their legendary conversation was about to unfold.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Japan</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/posts/japan/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 13 Sep 2024 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/posts/japan/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;The old apartment complexes in Japan are usually brick red, dusty off-white, or plain brown. They only come in these three listless color schemes. You can see them fairly well when taking the train, elevated off the street to save space. Buildings huddle together with just enough space in between for a single thin street. Story after story, door after door of rooms filled with families. It&amp;rsquo;s depressing to see humans relegated to this lifestyle—an overly intricate complex swarming with humans cramming every available hole. Just like a nest full of ants: ants of rudimentary intelligence, completing tasks for the sake of completing them, and living for the sake of being alive. It&amp;rsquo;s a melancholy sight, yet somehow beautiful—like watching nature at work. Like being god. Surely, in those moments, I must have had the eyes of god.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
